<resources>
    <string name="app_name">PostCutter</string>
    <string name="loading_text">Image is processing…</string>
    <string name="settings_suggestion_lines">move helper</string>
    <string name="save">save</string>
    <string name="cancel">cancel</string>
    <string name="settings_dialog_text">Edge calculation</string>
    <string name="text_erase_dialog_title">replace area with:</string>
    <string name="telea_method">Telea method</string>
    <string name="ns_method">NS method</string>
    <string name="save_as_new">save as new</string>
    <string name="delete_dialog_title">Do you want to delete this image?</string>
    <string name="delete">delete</string>
    <string name="cutter_save_dialog_title">Do you want to save this image?</string>
    <string name="cutter_title">set area for crop</string>
    <string name="text_erase_title">set area for content erase</string>
    <string name="fast">fast</string>
    <string name="accurate">accurate</string>
    <string name="reload">suggest again</string>
    <string name="permission_granted_text">Permissions granted.</string>
    <string name="permission_denied_text">Permissions denied. Permissions are required to use the app.</string>
    <string name="next">next</string>
    <string name="close">close</string>

    <string name="help_title">Tutorial</string>

    <string name="help_detail_button_crop">"By first button, it is start automatic crop for image."</string>
    <string name="help_detail_button_replace">"By second button, it is possible to remove text or watermark."</string>
    <string name="help_detail_button_share">"By third button, it is possible to share image."</string>
    <string name="help_detail_button_delete">"By fourth button, it is possible to permanently delete image."</string>

    <string name="help_rectangle_resize">"Move with one of the eight dots in corners and center of edges for frame resize."</string>
    <string name="help_rectangle_move">"Grab center area of frame for move without resize it."</string>

    <string name="help_crop_hide">"If the top and bottom bars are showed, then you couldn`t be able to manipulate with crop frame. For hide these bars click on display."</string>
    <string name="help_crop_show">"If you want to save the crop, you need press button on bottom bar. For show top and bottom bar again click on display."</string>
    <string name="help_crop_save">"For save the crop press the button on bottom bar."</string>
    <string name="help_crop_settings">"For crop settings press button in right corner of the top bar."</string>
    <string name="help_crop_accurate">"Accuracy setting set number of edge methods use for crop calculation. With more edge methods there is better change for crop to be set correct, but the process of calculation is longer."</string>
    <string name="help_crop_help_lines">"Move helper helping user to set edge of crop line on one of the edges on image in manual move."</string>
    <string name="help_crop_reload">"Reload start the process of finding crop again."</string>

    <string name="help_replace_hide">"If the bottom bar is showed, then you couldn`t be able to manipulate with frame for replace. For this the bar click on display."</string>
    <string name="help_replace_show">"If you want to save the image with replaced are, you need press button on bottom bar. For show this bar click again on display."</string>
    <string name="help_replace_save">"After position the area for replace press button on bottom. Then choose one of two images by which the area will be replace."</string>

    <string name="skip">skip</string>
</resources>